<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="app_name">The name of the application.
{{Identical|Wikimedia Commons}}</string>
  <string name="app_name_beta">Name of the beta version of the application</string>
  <string name="menu_refresh">Label for menu item that refreshes current list of images.</string>
  <string name="menu_settings">Label for menu item to show settings.
{{Identical|Settings}}</string>
  <string name="username">{{Identical|Username}}</string>
  <string name="password">{{Identical|Password}}</string>
  <string name="login">Button to have people log in.
{{Identical|Log in}}</string>
  <string name="logging_in_title">Title of dialog box shown while logging in.
{{Identical|Logging in}}</string>
  <string name="logging_in_message">Contents of dialog box shown while logging in.
{{Identical|Please wait}}</string>
  <string name="login_success">Message when login has succeeded.
{{Identical|Login successful}}</string>
  <string name="login_failed">Message when login has failed.
{{Identical|Login failed}}</string>
  <string name="authentication_failed">Message shown to user when authentication to Commons fails. Shown as a small toast that disappears after a while.</string>
  <string name="uploading_started">Toast message when uploading has started</string>
  <string name="upload_completed_notification_title">Title for notification about upload being completed. %1$s represents file name.
{{Identical|Uploaded}}</string>
  <string name="upload_completed_notification_text">Text for notification about upload being completed.</string>
  <string name="upload_progress_notification_title_start">Title for notificiation about upload being started. %1$s represents file name</string>
  <string name="upload_progress_notification_title_in_progress">Title for notification about upload being in progress. %1$s represents file name</string>
  <string name="upload_progress_notification_title_finishing">Title for notification about upload being completed. %1$s represents file name</string>
  <string name="upload_failed_notification_title">Title for notification about upload failing. %1$s represents file name</string>
  <string name="upload_failed_notification_subtitle">Text for notification about upload being completed.</string>
  <string name="title_activity_contributions">Title for screen showing my contributions.
{{Identical|My upload}}</string>
  <string name="contribution_state_queued">Show status of upload as currently queued.
{{Identical|Queue}}</string>
  <string name="contribution_state_failed">Show status of upload as failed.
{{Identical|Failed}}</string>
  <string name="contribution_state_in_progress">Show status of upload as currently in progress. %1$d%% represents percentage of current file that has been uploaded</string>
  <string name="contribution_state_starting">Show status of upload as about to start.
{{Identical|Uploading}}</string>
  <string name="menu_from_gallery">Action bar item to prompt the user to pick a picture from the phone to upload</string>
  <string name="menu_from_camera">Action bar item to allow the user to take a picture to upload</string>
  <string name="provider_contributions">Display name for user\'s contributions in the phone\'s settings sync screen.
{{Identical|My upload}}</string>
  <string name="menu_share">{{Identical|Share}}</string>
  <string name="menu_open_in_browser">Menu item that opens image in the browser.</string>
  <string name="share_title_hint">{{Identical|Title}}</string>
  <string name="share_description_hint">{{Identical|Description}}</string>
  <string name="login_failed_network">Error message shown to user when login can not be completed due to network issues.</string>
  <string name="login_failed_username">Error message shown to user when login can not be completed because the user name is wrong.</string>
  <string name="login_failed_password">Error message shown to user when login can not be completed beause the password is wrong</string>
  <string name="login_failed_throttled">Error message shown to user when login can not be completed because the user has attempted to login too many times in a short period of time, and hence been throttled.</string>
  <string name="login_failed_blocked">Error message shown to user when login can not be completed because the user is blocked on Wikimedia Commons</string>
  <string name="login_failed_generic">{{Identical|Login failed}}</string>
  <string name="share_upload_button">{{Identical|Upload}}</string>
  <string name="multiple_share_base_title">Hint for the textbox that lets user type the Base title for the set of multiple images being uploaded. Example: If the user types \'Visit to Kolkata\' in this text box, the images will all be titled as \'Visit to Kolkata - 1\', \'Visit to Kolkata - 2\', etc.</string>
  <string name="menu_upload_single">Hint text on menu item to upload a single image.
{{Identical|Upload}}</string>
  <string name="categories_search_text_hint">This message is followed by a list of the categories.
{{Identical|Search category}}</string>
  <string name="menu_save_categories">Hint text on menu item to save selected categories.
{{Identical|Save}}</string>
  <string name="categories_not_found">Message shown to the user when no category matching what they searched for was found. %1$s represents the category name</string>
  <string name="categories_skip_explanation">Text explaining to users why and how to add categories to images. Users can also tap this message to skip adding categories.</string>
  <string name="categories_activity_title">Title for the activity where Categories are being selected to add to the Image.
{{Identical|Category}}</string>
  <string name="preference_tracking">Text for preference that enables the user to enable or disable collection of data about the user\'s usage patterns.</string>
  <string name="preference_tracking_summary">Help text for preference that enables the user to enable or disable collection of data about the user\'s usage patterns.</string>
  <string name="title_activity_settings">{{Identical|Settings}}</string>
  <string name="menu_about">{{Identical|About}}</string>
  <string name="about_license">License</string>
  <string name="about_improve">Source and Bugs</string>
  <string name="about_privacy_policy">HTML fragment linking to Wikimedia\'s privacy policy. Note: avoid percent-encoding in the URL, as this causes problems with Android\'s resource compiler. Use accented/non-ASCII characters \"as is\" if possible. (We can fix it manually, so don\'t worry too much about it.)</string>
  <string name="title_activity_about">{{Identical|About}}</string>
  <string name="menu_feedback">Menu item text that prompts user to send feedback to WMF via email</string>
  <string name="waiting_first_sync">Message shown on contributions list during first sync.</string>
  <string name="no_uploads_yet">Message shown on contribution list during non-first sync if no uploads present.</string>
  <string name="menu_retry_upload">Menu item text prompting user to retry a failed upload.
{{Identical|Retry}}</string>
  <string name="menu_cancel_upload">Menu item text prompting user to cancel and delete a failed upload.</string>
  <string name="share_license_summary">Text label telling user the license of the current upload in progress. %1$s refers to appropriate display text for the chosen CC license</string>
  <string name="menu_download">Menu item text prompting user to download a selected photo or media file locally.
{{Identical|Download}}</string>
  <string name="preference_license">{{Identical|License}}</string>
  <string name="license_name_cc_by_sa">CC Attribution-Sharelike License display name. Use the non-breaking space character(u00A0) between \'CC\' and \'Attribution-Sharealike\'</string>
  <string name="license_name_cc_by">CC Attribution License display name. Use the non-breaking space character(u00A0) between \'CC\' and \'Attribution\'</string>
  <string name="license_name_cc0">CC0 License display name.</string>
  <string name="license_name_attribution">{{Identical|Attribution}}</string>
  <string name="welcome_wikipedia_text">Message inviting users to contribute their images.</string>
  <string name="welcome_wikipedia_subtext">Message explaining that Wikipedia images Wikimedia Commons.</string>
  <string name="welcome_copyright_text">Message explaining the educational benefit of contributing images.</string>
  <string name="welcome_copyright_subtext">Message explaining what kind of images not to submit.</string>
  <string name="welcome_final_text">Message asking user if they understand what kinds of images to upload.</string>
  <string name="welcome_final_button_text">Button text for confirming the user understands what kinds of images to upload.
{{Identical|Yes}}</string>
  <string name="detail_panel_cats_label">Label for categories list in media detail panel.
{{Identical|Category}}</string>
  <string name="detail_panel_cats_loading">Placeholder for categories list in media detail panel, while loading from network.
{{Identical|Loading}}</string>
  <string name="detail_panel_cats_none">Placeholder for categories list in media detail panel, if no categories found.
{{Identical|None selected}}</string>
</resources>
